(Q11（配对题）) ⭐ a remarkable range of sth —— 非常丰富的某物种类｜exhibit —— 展品
⭐ various —— 各种各样的｜collection —— 收藏品；收藏
⭐ give sb a taste of sth —— 让某人初步了解某事物
[Q11可能是干扰项(D)， 提到artist，但并不是D be given by artists] ⭐ for one thing —— 首先；一方面｜a fine collection of sth —— 优秀的大量收藏｜well-known artist —— 著名艺术家
⭐ recognise —— 认出；识别
[Q11答案句（E）attract largest number =  most popular] ⭐ attract visitors —— 吸引游客｜the largest number of... —— 数量最多的……｜before the crowds arrive —— 在人群到来之前
(Q12) ⭐ nineteenth-century —— 十九世纪的
[Q12答案句（D） donate=given] ⭐ donate —— 捐赠｜get sth started —— 使某事开始运行｜as it were —— 可以说；某种程度上
⭐ be of special interest to sb —— 对某人特别有吸引力/意义｜feel closer to —— 感觉与……更亲近
(Q13) ⭐ a number of —— 许多｜sculpture gallery —— 雕塑展厅｜closed for refurbishment —— 因翻修关闭
[Q13答案句（G） move = relocate] ⭐ come back —— 回来｜see sth properly —— 完整参观/充分了解某物｜move sth to... —— 将某物移动到……
(Q14) [Q14答案句（B） TV or newspaper = media] ⭐ temporary exhibition —— 临时展览｜see something about... —— 看到关于……的信息
⭐ create interest —— 引起兴趣｜present objects —— 展示物品｜continent —— 大洲
⭐ provide information about —— 提供关于……的信息｜social context —— 社会背景｜and so on —— 等等
(Q15) ⭐ collection of coins —— 硬币收藏
⭐ what you might call... —— 可以称为……｜focused collection —— 专门性的收藏｜specialist collection —— 专业收藏
[Q15答案句（C） ordinary people = members of the public] ⭐ ordinary people —— 普通人｜dig one's garden —— 挖掘花园土地｜donate to —— 捐赠给
(Q16) [Q16答案句（A）all was left to ... by ... =  one person] ⭐ porcelain —— 瓷器｜be left to sb —— 被遗赠给某人｜founder —— 创始人
⭐ in the terms of... —— 根据……条款｜will —— 遗嘱｜be allowed to do sth —— 被允许做某事｜perfect in itself —— 本身完美
(Q17（地图）) ⭐ practical information —— 实用信息｜in case —— 以防；如果
⭐ facility —— 设施｜downstairs —— 楼下｜basement —— 地下室
⭐ reach the bottom of... —— 到达……底部｜find yourself in... —— 发现自己处于……
⭐ have a rest —— 休息｜continue one's exploration of... —— 继续探索……
⭐ serve food —— 提供食物｜relaxing atmosphere —— 放松的氛围
[Q17答案句(找restaurant)] ⭐ go straight ahead —— 直走｜far side of... —— ……另一侧｜turn right into... —— 右转进入……
⭐ face sb —— 面向某人
(Q18) ⭐ have a snack —— 吃点心｜facilities for children —— 儿童设施
[Q18答案句(找cafe)] ⭐ immediately on the right —— 就在右侧
(Q19) ⭐ baby-changing facilities —— 婴儿护理设施
[Q19答案句(找baby-changing facilities)] ⭐ cross the area —— 穿过区域｜along the corridor —— 沿着走廊｜left-hand side —— 左侧
(Q20) ⭐ cloakroom —— 衣帽间｜leave sth somewhere —— 把某物放在某处
[Q20答案句(找cloakroom)] ⭐ through the door —— 经过门进入
⭐ on every floor —— 每一层｜the first room on the left —— 左侧第一个房间
⭐ leave something in the cloakroom —— 把东西寄存在衣帽间｜start our tour —— 开始参观